START	Start
DESCRIPTION_START	Start field. Every time you pass it, you get a %reward profit
CHANCE	Chance
DESCRIPTION_CHANCE	In this field you can get unscheduled income.
FORCE_MAJEURE	Force Majeure
DESCRIPTION_FORCE_MAJEURE	In this field, you incur losses from unforeseen events.
CUSTOMS	Customs
DESCRIPTION_CUSTOMS	It's a penalty field. If you move here from the Customs Clearance field, you will have to pay a %fine penalty or throw a
TAX	Tax
DESCRIPTION_TAX	In this field you will have to pay taxes amounting to 6% of your current capital.
OFFSHORE	Offshore
DESCRIPTION_OFFSHORE	Freedom from all taxes and duties. On this field you do not incur any costs and can relax.
GO_TO_CUSTOMS	Customs Clearance
DESCRIPTION_GO_TO_CUSTOMS	Your cargo is under arrest, go to the Customs penalty field, to exit from which you must pay a penalty of %fine or throw
DESCRIPTION_ROLLS_ROYCE	Rolls-Royce Motor Cars Limited is a British luxury automobile maker. A wholly owned subsidiary of German group BMW, it w
DESCRIPTION_MACDONALDS	McDonald's Corporation is an American fast food company, founded in 1940 as a restaurant operated by Richard and Maurice
DESCRIPTION_BP	BP is a multinational oil and gas company headquartered in London, England. It is one of the world's seven oil and gas "
DESCRIPTION_BBC	BBC (The British Broadcasting Corporation) is a British public service broadcaster. Its headquarters are at Broadcasting
DESCRIPTION_SAMSUNG	Samsung (Korean: 삼성; means "three stars" in English) is a South Korean multinational conglomerate headquartered in Samsu
DESCRIPTION_DANONE	Danone is a French multinational food-products corporation based in Paris and founded in Barcelona, Spain. The company i
DESCRIPTION_HENNESSY	Jas Hennessy & Co., commonly known simply as Hennessy, is a French brandy distiller with its headquarters located in Cog
DESCRIPTION_DISNEY	The Walt Disney Company, commonly known as Disney, is an American diversified multinational mass media and entertainment
DESCRIPTION_LOREAL	L'Oréal S.A. is a French personal care company headquartered in Clichy, Hauts-de-Seine with a registered office in Paris
DESCRIPTION_IKEA	IKEA is a multinational group that designs and sells ready-to-assemble furniture, kitchen appliances and home accessorie
DESCRIPTION_VOLVO	The Volvo Group is a Swedish multinational manufacturing company headquartered in Gothenburg. While its core activity is
DESCRIPTION_ARMANI	Giorgio Armani S.p.A. is an Italian luxury fashion house founded by Giorgio Armani which designs, manufactures, distribu
DESCRIPTION_VERSACE	Gianni Versace S.r.l., usually referred to simply as Versace, is an Italian luxury fashion company and trade name founde
DESCRIPTION_FERRARI	Ferrari is an Italian luxury sports car manufacturer based in Maranello. Founded by Enzo Ferrari in 1939, the company bu
DESCRIPTION_SONY	Sony Corporation is a Japanese multinational conglomerate corporation headquartered in Tokyo. Its diversified business i
DESCRIPTION_COCA	The Coca-Cola Company is an American multinational corporation, and manufacturer, retailer, and marketer of nonalcoholic
DESCRIPTION_CANON	Canon Inc. is a Japanese multinational corporation specializing in the manufacture of imaging and optical products, incl
DESCRIPTION_TOYOTA	Toyota Motor Corporation is a Japanese multinational automotive manufacturer headquartered in Toyota, Aichi, Japan. In 2
DESCRIPTION_HYUNDAI	The Hyundai Motor Company, commonly known as Hyundai Motors, is a South Korean multinational automotive manufacturer hea
DESCRIPTION_SIEMENS	Siemens AG is a German multinational conglomerate company headquartered in Munich and the largest industrial manufacturi
DESCRIPTION_ADIDAS	Adidas AG is a multinational corporation, founded and headquartered in Herzogenaurach, Germany, that designs and manufac
DESCRIPTION_FORD	Ford Motor Company, commonly known as Ford, is an American multinational automaker that has its main headquarters in Dea
DESCRIPTION_MERCEDES	Mercedes-Benz is a German global automobile marque and a division of Daimler AG. Mercedes-Benz is known for luxury vehic
DESCRIPTION_ALIBABA	Alibaba Group Holding Limited is a Chinese multinational technology company specializing in e-commerce, retail, Internet
DESCRIPTION_LENOVO	Lenovo Group Limited, is a Chinese multinational technology company with headquarters in Beijing. The company designs, d
DESCRIPTION_HUAWEI	Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. is a Chinese multinational technology company. It provides telecommunications equipment an
DESCRIPTION_XIAOMI	Xiaomi Corporation is a Chinese electronics company founded in April 2010 and headquartered in Beijing. Xiaomi makes and
DESCRIPTION_NESTLE	Nestlé S.A. is a Swiss multinational food and drink processing conglomerate corporation headquartered in Vevey, Vaud, Sw
DESCRIPTION_ROLEX	Rolex SA is a Swiss luxury watch manufacturer based in Geneva, Switzerland. As of June 2019, among the world's top ten m
